<Mod
	name="SpicyTP:Core"
	description="[h1]Spicy's Texture Pack: Core 1.0.2.0[/h1]
is the original resource pack for Noita. It aims to give most of the game a clean and unified aesthetic by way of many visual overhauls in one consistent style, including sleeker UI, more detailed materials, redesigned enemies, touched-up pixel scenes, and much more.
[h3]Join the Discord![/h3]
[url=https://discord.gg/4nN8KHBY6R]My personal Discord[/url] contains categories for things that I work on. I'd recommend joining if you're interested in seeing early previews of what's being worked on.

[hr][/hr]
[h2]What sprites does this mod overhaul?[/h2]
This mod currently supports:
[list]
[*]Vanilla - [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/discussion/2859751773/3372657164725020666]800 sprites[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2889150139]Pride Glimmers[/url] - [url=]16 sprites[/url]
[/list]
...and much more to come.

[h3]Toggles[/h3]
Toggles for most of the mod's features exist; they're on by default, and can be turned off to use their vanilla versions. The following is a list of what can't be toggled off, usually due to hardcoding:
[list]
[*]Generic, HUD, inventory, and infobox UI elements
[*]The lightning ray particle
[/list]

[h3]See also[/h3]
To further customize your visuals, be sure to visit the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2887423419]STP collection on the Steam Workshop[/url] or the [url=https://github.com/SpicySpaceSnake/SpicyTP/wiki]STP GitHub repository's wiki[/url].

[hr][/hr]
[h2]Is this mod compatible with X?[/h2]
SpicyTP is a relative friendly mod and really shouldn't break anything.
At most, a Mod X that overrites the same files or edits the same sections of files as SpicyTP may take priority over this mod if Mod X loads after it; likewise, this mod will take priority over others, though that's usually beneficial due to the nature of a texture pack.

[b]Found a bug? Leave a comment or start a discussion![/b]

[hr][/hr]
[h2]Will there ever be cross-mod support?[/h2]
[b]Yes![/b] There's already a fair bit of cross-mod content that I want to do (alongside further vanilla content updates), although I don't know what exactly I'll be doing next or when I'll do it.
Also, I'm not familiar with every mod out there! If you're the owner of (or somehow affiliated with) a mod that you want me to add support for, consider reaching out to ask.

[hr][/hr]
[h2]How often does this mod update?[/h2]
Updates are fairly sparse, likely taking about 1-3 months if not more; biomes are hefty and large, and I'm currently undergoing several life changes that hinder my ability to make art in one way or another.
In practice, this varies; after all, this is merely a hobby project, and other things may take complete priority over this mod.

[b]CURRENT PRIMARY FOCUS(ES)[/b]
[list]
[*]Temple of the Art
[*]Holy Mountains
[*]The Laboratory/The Work (End)
[/list]

[b]CURRENT SECONDARY FOCUS(ES)[/b]
[list]
[*]Projectiles
[*]Items
[/list]

[b]CURRENT STATUS:[/b] in backburner development

[i]Status last verified Jan 5, 2024
Mod last updated Jan 5, 2024[/i]

[hr][/hr]
[h2]Credits[/h2]
[list]
[*][b]SpicySpaceSnake[/b] ([url=https://spicyspacesnake.carrd.co]that's me![/url]): main artist
[*][b]Copi[/b] (@Human#6606 / [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/Copioush]Copi[/url]): programming the mod's spell icon replacement method and providing much-needed help with various other bits of code
[*][b]Conga Lyne[/b] (@Conga Lyne#2452 / [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/CongaLyne]Conga Lyne[/url]): teaching me to use and providing me with NXML and creature stain map generation
[*][b]Viowlet[/b] ([url=https://www.reddit.com/user/Viowlet]u/Viowlet[/url]): their [url=https://www.reddit.com/r/noita/comments/jp56ub/a_while_ago_i_made_noita_blackletter_this_is_now]free-to-use Noita Blackletter font[/url]
[/list]
[h3]A special thanks to[/h3]
[list]
[*][b]Siris[/b], for being a partial inspiration for the SpicyTP series
[*][b]Kirisis[/b], for being the light of my life and for her invaluable support and early feedback
[*][b]All of my partners[/b], for being a bunch of absolutely amazing people
[*][b]The many modders[/b] that I've either worked with or gotten advice from, for their previous and continued support

[*]and [b]YOU[/b], for taking the time to check out this mod!
[/list]

Please be sure to rate on your way out, and share this with anyone you think might like it. Happy Noiting!"
	tags="graphics, quality of life, spells, items, creatures, biomes"
	dont_upload_folders=""
	dont_upload_files=""
> 
</Mod>